jins.com 2016-08-14

# Privacy policy | JINS

Updated Feb 1, 2014.

JINS Eyewear US, Inc. (“JINS”) is committed to protecting your privacy, and this Policy describes the type of information we collect through our website and how it may be used, transferred, or disclosed.

  * Site Not for Use by Children
  * Changes to the Privacy Policy
  * How We Collect Information
  * Types of Information We Collect
  * How We Use Your Information
  * Disclosures of Information to Third Parties
  * Cookies
  * Health Information Collection
  * California Do Not Track Notice
  * Choosing to Not Receive Promotional Emails
  * Protecting Your Information
  * Third Party Sites
  * Inquiries

### Site Not for Use by Children

Our website, products and services are not intended for use by children under the age of eighteen (18), and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children. Please refer to our Terms of Use that prohibit children from sending us information via our website. If we discover that children have sent us personal information, we will take all reasonable measures to promptly delete such information. Adults are welcome to place orders on behalf of children.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

JINS reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy. An updated or modified Privacy Policy will be posted on this website and shall include the date it was last updated. The changes to the Privacy Policy shall be effective as of the date of posting. Your use of this website confirms that you agree to the most current Privacy Policy.

### How We Collect Information

We collect information based on the information that you provide to us, and information from your use of our website. You must provide your personal information if you want to do things such as make purchases or create an account. Once you have created an account, you will be able to edit your personal information in the [account settings](http://www.jins.com/us/customer/account/). 

### Types of Information We Collect

The information we collect when you visit our website depends on things such as your browser settings, what information you actively provide us, and what links you click on. The following information is information that we collect when you choose to provide it to us by actively sending it to us through our website: 

  * Your name;
  * Your mailing address;
  * Your email address;
  * Your telephone number;
  * Names you use on social media sites;
  * Photographs (such as a photo of your face to enable you to try on glasses virtually); and
  * Credit card information.

In addition to the information you actively send us, we may also automatically collect information such as Internet protocol (IP) addresses, the type of Internet browser you are using, your Internet service provider (ISP), the pages through which you entered or exited our website, the path you navigated through our website, the operating system of your computer or device, and date and time information. We collect and store such automatically gathered information on an individual and aggregate basis.

### How We Use Your Information

We use information that you provide to us to process your orders, answer inquiries, contact you when necessary, improve customer service, and other internal business purposes. We use the information gathered from your use of the website to analyze website usage trends, administer and improve the website, and compile information about the types of people who visit and use our website.

### Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

We may share your information with third party contractors we have engaged to support our operations. Third party contractors may perform services such as sending emails, maintaining our website, processing and authorizing payment, fulfilling or shipping orders, or analyzing data. Our third party contractors are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

Other than as described in this Privacy Policy or with your approval, we do not rent, sell, or otherwise disclose your information to any third parties.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that is stored on your computer or device for record-keeping purposes when you visit a website. Cookies may store information about your preferences or usage of the website. We may link the information we store in cookies to your personal information in order to provide a faster and more efficient online experience. You can choose to delete existing cookies and/or disable future cookies. Please note that if you disable future cookies, you may still use our website, but certain functionality or features may be limited. We use both session cookies and persistent cookies on this website.

We use temporary “session cookies” to make it easier for you to navigate our site. We use session cookies to record session information, such as which web pages you have visited, and to track your activity on the site. We also use session cookies to store any passwords used on the site (such as a password associated with your user account), so you don't have to enter your password more than once per session. Session cookies expire when you explicitly log out, or after 90 days from your last login.

We use persistent cookies to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Persistent cookies remain on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can delete persistent cookies by following directions provided in your browser's "help" file.

### Health Information Collection

We maintain the privacy of your health information in accordance with the requirements of applicable federal and state law. Please see our [HIPAA Privacy Statement](http://www.jins.com/us/hipaa-statement) for details about your rights concerning your health information. Any health information we collect from you on this site will be handled in accordance with the terms of our HIPAA Privacy Statement.

### California Do Not Track Notice

We do not collect or track your information over time and across third party websites, and therefore we do not respond to “do not track” (DNT) signals. [Third parties that have content or services on our website, such a social feature or analytics service, may obtain information about your usage of this website, but these third parties cannot collect any of your personally identifiable information from our website unless you directly provide it to them.] We never share your personal information with third parties for direct marketing purposes.

### Choosing to Not Receive Promotional Emails

If you do not wish to receive promotional emails or newsletters from us, please let us know by selecting the option to not receive such emails when you create your account. Also every promotional email or newsletter we send will have a link that allows you to unsubscribe and stop receiving all promotional emails or newsletters in the future.

Please note that even if you choose to not receive promotional emails or newsletters, we may still email you administrative notices about this site or informational notices concerning your product orders or account.

### Protecting Your Information

We understand the importance of maintaining the security of your personal information, and we follow commercially-reasonable and generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information you submit to us. When you enter sensitive and/or personally-identifying information during registration or while ordering, we encrypt the transmissions involving such information using secure protocols. 

Please note that while we encrypt the data for your protection, we do not guarantee that your information is 100% secure. By sending us data, you are agreeing that we do not guarantee the security of such data, but that we will endeavor to protect it using commercially-reasonable and generally accepted industry standards. 

### Third Party Sites

This Policy applies only to information collected by this website. This website may contain links to other websites that are not owned or operated by JINS (“Third Party Sites”). We do not provide your information to Third Party Sites, and we do not control the collection or use of any information on or by Third Party Sites. Accordingly, we make no representations about how Third Party Sites use your information. This means that a link from our site to a Third Party Site can take you to a page that does not follow this Policy. If you choose to disclose personal information to any Third Party Sites, we encourage you to read the privacy policies of those sites.

### Inquiries

If you have questions or concerns about this Policy, please [contact us](http://www.jins.com/us/contact-us).
